(Penny:)Oh, thanks for asking
until I did.
(Amy:)Hear, hear.
(Leonard:)Cheers.
(Alfred:)I, uh, I would also like
to make a toast.
(Sheldon:)Aw.
(chuckles)
Leonard,
(Alfred:)I am so happy
that you have found a woman
(Alfred:)who loves and cares for you.
(Beverly:)What the hell is that
supposed to mean?
(Alfred:)Why don't you take a pill?
(Beverly:)Like you did before sex?
(Alfred:)What I really needed
(Alfred:)was a blindfold.
All right, everyone...
calm down.
Let's all remember what
it says in the Bible:
"He who is slow to anger
is better than the mighty."
(Beverly:)Oh, dear woman, can you please
read another book?
(Mary:)When God writes one, I will.
(clears throat)
Um, if-if we want to order
the soufflé,
(Penny:)we might want to get on that.